<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
     <string name="accessibility_enabled">เปิดใช้สิ่งอำนวยความสะดวกแล้ว</string>
     <string name="agree">ตกลง</string>
     <string name="agree_and_next">Agree</string>
     <string name="agree_terms">ฉันได้อ่านและยอมรับข้อตกลงการใช้บริการและนโยบายความเป็นส่วนตัวแล้ว</string>
     <string name="agree_terms_input_method_facemoji">ฉันได้อ่านและเห็นด้วยกับนโยบายความเป็นส่วนตัว Facemoji</string>
     <string name="agree_terms_input_method_kika">ฉันได้อ่านและเห็นด้วยกับนโยบายความเป็นส่วนตัว Kika</string>
     <string name="ai_button_desc">รับสิทธิ์เข้าถึงการสั่งงานด้วยเสียงอัจฉริยะของคุณโดยทันที</string>
     <string name="ai_button_double_press">กดสองครั้ง</string>
     <string name="ai_button_double_press_desc">กดปุ่ม AI สองครั้งเพื่อเสร็จสิ้นงานที่กำหนดเอง</string>
     <string name="ai_button_long_press">กดค้าง</string>
     <string name="ai_button_long_press_desc">กดค้างที่ปุ่ม AI เพื่อพูดกับ Mi AI</string>
     <string name="ai_button_single_press">กด</string>
     <string name="ai_button_single_press_desc">กดปุ่ม AI เพื่อดูปุ่มลัด Mi AI</string>
     <string name="ai_button_title">ปุ่ม AI</string>
     <string name="album_introduction">Gallery allows you to manage, optimize, and edit photos and videos on your device, as well as sync them to Xiaomi Cloud.</string>
     <string name="app_name">บทบัญญัติ</string>
     <string name="application_package_introduction">This app allows you to install third party apps, scan them before installation, and give recommendations after it.</string>
     <string name="application_permissions">การอนุญาตแอป</string>
     <string name="back">ย้อนกลับ</string>
     <string name="calculator_introduction">You can use this app for calculations, converting units and currencies, and estimating your mortgage repayments.</string>
     <string name="camera_introduction">You can use Camera to take photos and shoot videos.</string>
     <string name="carrier_introduction">In order to provide you with better services, your device may periodically send your device version information, device identification data (including IMEI/IMSI/MSISDN/MAC address, MEID/ICCID), and approximate location information (including base station ID) to the carrier via WLAN, mobile data network, or free SMS. The carrier promises to analyze relevant information only to improve the quality of services or to provide customized services or technologies, and won&apos;t disclose relevant information to third parties in any form that identifies you personally. The specific carrier statement shall prevail. Consult your carrier regarding the cost of using this service.</string>
     <string name="clock_introduction">You can use this app to view time, as well as use timer, world clock, stopwatch, set alarms, and more.</string>
     <string name="close_location_service_setting">You can choose turn off location access in Settings &gt; Additional settings &gt; Privacy or restrict permissions for individual apps in Security.</string>
     <string name="cm_terms_content">เพื่อปรับปรุงการบริการที่ดีขึ้นให้กับคุณ ผู้ดำเนินการเครือข่ายมือถือที่คุณเลือกอาจอัปโหลดข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลและข้อมูลเกี่ยวกับอุปกรณ์นี้ไปยังเซิร์ฟเวอร์โดยใช้เครือข่าย Wi-Fi หรือการเชื่อมต่อข้อมูลมือถือ ข้อมูลนี้จะถูกใช้เพื่อวัตถุประสงค์ทางสถิติเท่านั้นเพื่อปรับปรุงคุณภาพของบริการและให้เนื้อหาที่เป็นส่วนตัวมากขึ้น ข้อมูลนี้จะไม่ถูกใช้เพื่อระบุตัวคุณเป็นการส่วนตัวและจะไม่ถูกเปิดเผยต่อบุคคลที่สาม</string>
     <string name="cm_terms_title">ข้อตกลงผู้ให้บริการเครือข่ายมือถือ</string>
     <string name="compass_introduction">You can use this app for navigation, as well as viewing coordinates, atmospheric pressure, and altitude.</string>
     <string name="congratulation_label">ไปลองใช้กันเลย!</string>
     <string name="congratulation_swipe">ปัดขึ้นเพื่อเข้าสู่ระบบ</string>
     <string name="congratulation_title">ตั้งค่าเสร็จสิ้น</string>
     <string name="content_description_complete">เสร็จสมบูรณ์</string>
     <string name="content_description_miui_version">MIUI 10</string>
     <string name="content_description_start">เริ่มต้น</string>
     <string name="content_introduction">Content Center aggregates content and services from multiple channels. Here you can read articles, watch videos, view daily featured items, and receive content recommendations.</string>
     <string name="continue_to_enable_accessibility">แตะสองนิ้วค้างเพื่อเปิดใช้งานสิ่งอำนวยความสะดวก</string>
     <string name="desc_extra_fingerprint" />
     <string name="desc_extra_international_fingerprint" />
     <string name="desc_fingerprint">ใช้ลายนิ้วมือของคุณในการปลดล็อกเครื่อง ชำระเงินผ่าน Mi Pay หรือใช้เพื่อเข้าสู่ระบบของแอปหรือบริการต่างๆ</string>
     <string name="desc_international_fingerprint">ใช้ลายนิ้วมือของคุณในการปลดล็อกเครื่อง ลงชื่อเข้าสู่แอปหรือบริการต่างๆ</string>
     <string name="diagnose_report">Send diagnostic data to locate and analyze system issues and improve user experience. Such data may include personal information (e.g. IP, location, etc.)</string>
     <string name="disageement_abnormal_download">If you don&apos;t agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won&apos;t be able to use this service.</string>
     <string name="disagree">ยกเลิก</string>
     <string name="disagreement_abnormal_running">If you don&apos;t agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won&apos;t be able to use this app. You can choose not to use this app or restrict permissions in the Settings in such cases.</string>
     <string name="disagreement_donnot_use_application">If you don&apos;t agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won&apos;t be able to use this app. You can choose not to use this app in such cases.</string>
     <string name="disagreement_donnot_use_product">If you don&apos;t agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won&apos;t be able to use this product. You can choose not to use this product in such cases.</string>
     <string name="disagreement_donnot_use_service">If you don&apos;t agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won&apos;t be able to use this service. You can choose not to use this service in such cases.</string>
     <string name="disagreement_exit_app">If you don&apos;t agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won&apos;t be able to use this app. You can choose to sign out or restrict permissions in the Settings in such cases.</string>
     <string name="disagreement_function">If you don&apos;t agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won&apos;t be able to use this feature. You can choose not to use this feature in such cases.</string>
     <string name="disagreement_location_service">If you don&apos;t agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won&apos;t be able to use this service.</string>
     <string name="disagreement_terminate_service">If you don&apos;t agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won&apos;t be able to use this app. You can choose to uninstall, sign out, or restrict permissions in the Settings in such cases.</string>
     <string name="download_introduction">This app manages all your downloads, including those done in GetApps, Mi Video, Updater, Themes, and Browser.</string>
     <string name="enable_accessibility_canceled">ยกเลิกสิ่งอำนวยความสะดวกแล้ว</string>
     <string name="enable_accessibility_dialog_message">แตะสองนิ้วบนหน้าจอค้างไว้ 10 วิ เพื่อเปิด TalkBack, TalkBack ให้การตอบรับด้วยเสียงสำหรับผู้ที่มีความบกพร่องทางสายตา ถ้าคุณเปิดใช้งานโดยไม่ได้ตั้งใจให้แตะปุ่มยกเลิกแล้วแตะสองครั้งที่หน้าจอ</string>
     <string name="enable_accessibility_dialog_negative_btn">ยกเลิก</string>
     <string name="enable_accessibility_dialog_positive_btn">ตกลง</string>
     <string name="fast_application_introduction">Quick apps Framework allows you to create and provide services in quick apps.</string>
     <string name="font_hint_large">ค่าเริ่มต้นขนาดข้อความ</string>
     <string name="font_hint_normal">เพิ่มขนาดข้อความ</string>
     <string name="framework_introduction">Mi Services Framework allows you to use Mi Account, Mi Push, Mi Stats, and MIUI BI.</string>
     <string name="framwork_base_service">To provide you with these services, Mi Services Framework (MiAccount, Mi Push, Mi Stats, MIUI BI) needs to connect to the internet, access your phone number, IMEI, and IMSI, and allow your device to receive push notifications</string>
     <string name="game_introduction">Games plug-in allows you to sign in, create orders, complete payments, use coupons, and participate in promotion events.</string>
     <string name="google_service_introduction">To be able to work normally, Google Play needs to connect to the internet, access your location, be able to record audio, make calls, access calendar events, call history, sensors, storage, camera, device info, and accounts.</string>
     <string name="ime_privacy_policy">นโยบายความเป็นส่วนตัวสำหรับแป้นพิมพ์ที่เลือก</string>
     <string name="ime_privacy_policy_no_network">ไม่พบการเชื่อมต่อเครือข่าย กรุณาอ่านนโยบายความเป็นส่วนตัวของแป้นพิมพ์นี้ได้จาก %s</string>
     <string name="input_method_category">กรุณาเลือกแป้นพิมพ์ที่คุณต้องการใช้เป็นค่าเริ่มต้นในการเขียนข้อความ, บันทึกย่อหรืออื่นๆ คุณสามารถเลือกติดตั้งแป้นพิมพ์ภายนอกเพิ่มได้ในภายหลัง</string>
     <string name="input_method_setting">เลือกแป้นพิมพ์</string>
     <string name="install_preinstall_app">กำลังโหลดแอปต่างๆ…</string>
     <string name="item_fingerprint">ลายนิ้วมือ</string>
     <string name="item_lock_screen_password">เฉพาะล็อกหน้าจอ</string>
     <string name="language_picker_other_languages_title">ภาษาเพิ่มเติม</string>
     <string name="language_settings">เลือกภาษา</string>
     <string name="locale_picker_other_locale_title">พื้นที่อื่นๆ</string>
     <string name="locale_picker_title">เลือกพื้นที่ของคุณ</string>
     <string name="location_introduction">Location-based services find products and services near you.</string>
     <string name="lockscreen_introduction">Wallpaper Carousel allows you to get fresh images delivered to your Lock screen daily.</string>
     <string name="miui_privacy_policy_no_network">คุณไม่ได้เชื่อมกับต่ออินเตอร์เน็ต กรุณาอ่านนโยบายความเป็นส่วนตัวได้ที่ %s</string>
     <string name="miui_terms_no_network">คุณไม่ได้เชื่อมกับต่ออินเตอร์เน็ต กรุณาอ่านข้อตกลงและเงื่อนไขการให้บริการได้ที่ %s</string>
     <string name="multisim_settings_category">ตั้งค่าซิมการ์ด</string>
     <string name="multisim_settings_title">ระบบพบซิมการ์ดจำนวน 2 ซิม</string>
     <string name="navigation_picker_gesture_guide">แนะนำท่าทาง</string>
     <string name="navigation_picker_radio_text_full_screen">ท่าทางสัมผัสแบบเต็มหน้าจอ</string>
     <string name="navigation_picker_radio_text_virtual_key">ปุ่ม</string>
     <string name="next">ถัดไป</string>
     <string name="next_fingerprint">ถัดไป</string>
     <string name="note_introduction">This app allows you to create, view, and edit notes.</string>
     <string name="other_settings">ตั้งค่าเพิ่มเติม</string>
     <string name="other_settings_ad_dialog_content">After turning this feature off, you&apos;ll no longer receive personalized ads. However, you&apos;ll still receive ads that are irrelevant to your interests. You can learn more about personalized ads in Xiaomi Privacy Policy.
Turn off personalized ads anyway?</string>
     <string name="other_settings_ad_disable_summary">Turn on to personalize ads</string>
     <string name="other_settings_ad_enable">การแนะนำเกี่ยวกับโฆษณาส่วนบุคคล</string>
     <string name="other_settings_ad_enable_summary">รับโฆษณาที่ปรับเปลี่ยนในแบบของคุณตามข้อมูลพฤติกรรมของคุณ</string>
     <string name="other_settings_auto_update">อัพเดทโดยอัตโนมัติ</string>
     <string name="other_settings_auto_update_summary">MIUI จะเลือกเวลาที่ดีที่สุดในการติดตั้งการอัปเดต</string>
     <string name="other_settings_enhanced_lockscreen">ภาพพื้นหลังรายวัน</string>
     <string name="other_settings_enhanced_lockscreen_privacy_index">Privacy Policy</string>
     <string name="other_settings_enhanced_lockscreen_summary">รับรูปภาพและเรื่องราวที่จัดไว้ให้กับหน้าจอล็อกของคุณทุกวัน ตามข้อตกลงและเงื่อนไข</string>
     <string name="other_settings_enhanced_lockscreen_summary_index">ข้อตกลงและเงื่อนไข</string>
     <string name="other_settings_location">ตำแหน่งพิกัด</string>
     <string name="other_settings_location_summary">อนุญาตให้แอปเข้าถึงตำแหน่งพิกัดของคุณ</string>
     <string name="other_settings_upload_debug_log_summary">สถิติการใช้งานที่ช่วยให้เราค้นหาและแก้ไขปัญหา อาจมีข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลของคุณ</string>
     <string name="other_settings_upload_debug_log_title">ส่งข้อมูลการวินิจฉัยโดยอัตโนมัติ</string>
     <string name="other_settings_user_experience">โปรแกรมประสบการณ์ผู้ใช้</string>
     <string name="other_settings_user_experience_summary">ช่วยพัฒนาสินค้าและบริการของเรา​ด้วยการแชร์สถิติการใช้ของคุณกับเรา เรียกดูรายละเอียด</string>
     <string name="other_settings_user_experience_summary_index">เรียกดูรายละเอียด</string>
     <string name="permission_account">Access accounts on your device:</string>
     <string name="permission_account_introduction">For signing in with Mi Account</string>
     <string name="permission_application_package_introduction">For accessing storage in order to parse and scan installation packages</string>
     <string name="permission_call_records">Access call history:</string>
     <string name="permission_call_records_introduction">For accessing call history in order to display blocked items</string>
     <string name="permission_call_state_introduction">For accessing phone status, recording calls, and pausing recordings during incoming calls</string>
     <string name="permission_clock_info_introduction">For saving alarm data</string>
     <string name="permission_contact">Access contacts:</string>
     <string name="permission_contact_introduction">For providing Blocklist functionality and calling emergency contacts</string>
     <string name="permission_different_device_introduction">For identifying services associated with different devices</string>
     <string name="permission_different_info_introduction">For identifying different devices</string>
     <string name="permission_direct_call">Make calls:</string>
     <string name="permission_direct_call_introduction">For adding items to Blocklist</string>
     <string name="permission_download_introduction">For caching downloaded items and saving them on your device</string>
     <string name="permission_imei_service">For accessing IMEI to provide services associated with your device</string>
     <string name="permission_interaction_introduction">For saving photos and videos on device</string>
     <string name="permission_location">Access location info:</string>
     <string name="permission_location_introduction">For providing location-based services</string>
     <string name="permission_log_introduction">For saving logs</string>
     <string name="permission_login_introduction">For signing in and managing system accounts</string>
     <string name="permission_message_introduction">For sending messages to blocked contacts</string>
     <string name="permission_phone_imei_device">For accessing IMEI in order to identify devices</string>
     <string name="permission_phone_network">For accessing network type in order to optimize and adjust downloadable items</string>
     <string name="permission_phone_service">Access phone number, IMEI, and IMSI:</string>
     <string name="permission_photo_introduction">For saving images to Gallery and publishing statuses</string>
     <string name="permission_photo_video">Take photos and record video:</string>
     <string name="permission_photo_video_introduction">For taking photos, recording videos, and using flash</string>
     <string name="permission_picture_introduction">For saving, editing, and syncing photos and videos</string>
     <string name="permission_read_call_records">Edit call history:</string>
     <string name="permission_read_call_records_introduction">For adding items to call history and deleting blocked calls</string>
     <string name="permission_read_note_introduction">For accessing notes and attachments</string>
     <string name="permission_read_write_file">Access and save files and photos on your device:</string>
     <string name="permission_read_write_file_introduction">For accessing, saving, and caching items on your device</string>
     <string name="permission_recorder_file_introduction">For accessing and saving audio recordings</string>
     <string name="permission_recording">Record calls and audio:</string>
     <string name="permission_recording_introduction">For recording audio while recording video</string>
     <string name="permission_screen_shoot_introduction">For accessing and saving screen recordings</string>
     <string name="permission_send_message">Send SMS</string>
     <string name="permission_user_record_introduction">For recording audio</string>
     <string name="permission_virusscan_introduction">For performing virus scan and optimizing your device</string>
     <string name="permission_xunlei_introduction">For signing in and managing system accounts in order to provide Xunlei services</string>
     <string name="poco_agree_terms_other">(รวมถึงนโยบายความเป็นส่วนตัวและข้อตกลงผู้ใช้ ของ POCO launcher)</string>
     <string name="pref_title_data_slot">ซิมที่ใช้งานข้อมูลเป็นหลัก</string>
     <string name="pref_title_voice_slot">ซิมที่ใช้โทรออกเป็นหลัก</string>
     <string name="privacy_policy">นโยบายความเป็นส่วนตัว</string>
     <string name="protect_persoanl_info_statement">We shall protect your personal information in accordance with the relevant laws, regulations, and privacy policies.</string>
     <string name="provision_inputmethod_policy_description">"
แสดงนโยบายความเป็นส่วนตัวของแป้นพิมพ์ที่เลือก"</string>
     <string name="provision_inputmethod_policy_description1">นโยบายความเป็นส่วนตัว</string>
     <string name="recorder_introduction">You can use this app to record audio and back up recordings to the cloud.</string>
     <string name="require_authority_statement">To allow us to provide you with basic services, you need to grant the following permissions in order for us to collect your personal information:</string>
     <string name="require_network_authority_statement">To allow us to provide you with basic services, you need to connect to the internet and grant the following permissions in order for us to collect your personal information:</string>
     <string name="screen_recording_introduction">This app allows you to record what&apos;s happening on your screen.</string>
     <string name="security_introduction">You can use this app to clear trash on your device, find and neutralize viruses, optimize performance for gaming, save battery, manage apps, and more.</string>
     <string name="security_mobile_account_introduction">For signing in and managing system accounts</string>
     <string name="service_agreement">I&apos;ve read and agreed to the terms and conditions.</string>
     <string name="service_name_album">Gallery</string>
     <string name="service_name_application_package">Package installer</string>
     <string name="service_name_calculator">Calculator</string>
     <string name="service_name_camera">Camera</string>
     <string name="service_name_carrier">Statement on carrier services</string>
     <string name="service_name_clock">Clock</string>
     <string name="service_name_compass">Compass</string>
     <string name="service_name_content_center">Content Center</string>
     <string name="service_name_download">Downloads</string>
     <string name="service_name_fast_application">Quick apps Framework</string>
     <string name="service_name_game">Games plug-in</string>
     <string name="service_name_google_service">Statement on Google services</string>
     <string name="service_name_location">Location-based services</string>
     <string name="service_name_lockscreen">Wallpaper Carousel</string>
     <string name="service_name_note">Notes</string>
     <string name="service_name_recorder">Recorder</string>
     <string name="service_name_screen_recording">Screen Recorder</string>
     <string name="service_name_security">Security</string>
     <string name="service_name_service_framework">Mi Services Framework</string>
     <string name="service_policy"><Data>Read and agree to our &lt;a href=%1$s>Privacy Policy&lt;/a >.</Data></string>
     <string name="service_privacy_index">Privacy Policy</string>
     <string name="servicestate_title">Statement on basic services</string>
     <string name="setting_locale">การตั้งค่าพื้นที่…</string>
     <string name="shut_down">ปิดเครื่อง</string>
     <string name="sim_card_detecting">กำลังตรวจหาซิมการ์ด…</string>
     <string name="sim_card_detecting_check">ไม่พบซิมการ์ด ตรวจสอบให้แน่ใจว่าซิมการ์ดถูกติดตั้งอย่างเหมาะสม และตรวจสอบว่ามียอดเงินคงเหลืออยู่</string>
     <string name="sim_card_detecting_confirm_turn_on_network">อนุญาตให้เชื่อมต่อกับเครือข่ายข้อมูลมือถือหรือไม่? หากคุณทำเช่นนั้นซิมการ์ดที่คุณใส่จะใช้เพื่อเชื่อมต่อกับเครือข่ายข้อมูลมือถือ</string>
     <string name="sim_card_detecting_title">ตรวจสอบซิมการ์ด</string>
     <string name="sim_card_detection">กรุณาใส่ซิมการ์ด</string>
     <string name="sim_card_detection_info">กรุณาใส่ซิมการ์ดและอ่านคำแนะนำที่ได้รับมาพร้อมกับอุปกรณ์ของคุณ</string>
     <string name="sim_card_detection_mobile_not_available">ซิมการ์ดไม่สามารถเชื่อมต่อกับเครือข่ายได้</string>
     <string name="sim_dectection_next">ทำต่อ</string>
     <string name="sim_redetection">ตรวจสอบอีกครั้ง</string>
     <string name="sim_scard_detecting_check_mobile_not_available">ซิมการ์ดของคุณไม่สามารถเชื่อมต่อกับเครือข่ายผู้ให้บริการที่ถูกต้อง ตรวจสอบให้แน่ใจว่าคุณมียอดเงินคงเหลือเพียงพอและลองเชื่อมต่ออีกครั้ง</string>
     <string name="skip_gesture_guide_dialog_message">ตรวจสอบให้แน่ใจว่าคุณทราบวิธีการใช้ท่าทางสัมผัสแบบเต็มหน้าจอก่อนเลือกตัวเลือกนี้</string>
     <string name="skip_gesture_guide_dialog_negative_btn">ยกเลิก </string>
     <string name="skip_gesture_guide_dialog_positive_btn">ตกลง</string>
     <string name="skip_gesture_guide_dialog_title">ท่าทางสัมผัสแบบเต็มหน้าจอ</string>
     <string name="skip_underline">ข้ามขั้นตอนนี้</string>
     <string name="start_up_slogan">ดีไซนด์เพื่อประสบการณ์แบบเต็มจอ</string>
     <string name="suggested_actions_uri">android.resource://com.android.provision/raw/suggested_actions</string>
     <string name="summary_not_set">ไม่ตั้งค่า</string>
     <string name="system_navigation_mode">โหมดนำทางระบบ</string>
     <string name="terms_of_use">ข้อตกลงและเงื่อนไข</string>
     <string name="terms_of_use_ble_htmlViewer">, Fused Location Provider, HTMLViewer</string>
     <string name="terms_of_use_label">"ความเป็นส่วนตัวของคุณเป็นสิ่งสำคัญมากสำหรับเรา โปรดอ่านข้อตกลงการใช้บริการและนโยบายความเป็นส่วนตัวของเราที่จะเข้าใจข้อมูลที่เรารวบรวมวิธีการที่เราใช้มันและตัวเลือกที่มีให้คุณ. 

คุณจะต้องยอมรับข้อกำหนดในการให้บริการและนโยบายส่วนบุคคลก่อนจึงจะสามารถ ใช้ MIUI %s และบัญชี Mi​ ส่วนประกอบสถิติจะเชื่อมต่อกับอินเทอร์เน็ตและตรวจสอบตำแหน่งของคุณ"</string>
     <string name="terms_of_use_label_Mistore">, Mi Store system plug-in</string>
     <string name="terms_of_use_label_mab">, MAB</string>
     <string name="terms_of_use_label_package">, Package installer</string>
     <string name="terms_of_use_label_phrase">, Frequent phrases</string>
     <string name="terms_of_use_label_systemhelper">, บริการลงทะเบียนด้วยตนเอง</string>
     <string name="terms_of_use_label_updater">, ตัวอัพเดท</string>
     <string name="terms_of_use_lable_apps">บริการ Mi, การเปิดใช้งานบริการ Mi SIM, Mi คลาวด์, ค้นหาอุปกรณ์, หน้าจอหลัก, ศูนย์เกมส์, MAB, MIUI Daemon และ ระบบส่วนประกอบ MSA, บริการการแปล, แอปด่วน, App vault, สถิติ, Mi Link</string>
     <string name="terms_of_use_lable_default_input_method_facemoji">"

คุณต้องยอมรับนโยบายความเป็นส่วนตัวของ Facemoji ก่อนที่จะใช้คุณลักษณะนี้"</string>
     <string name="terms_of_use_lable_default_input_method_kika">"

คุณต้องยอมรับนโยบายความเป็นส่วนตัวของ Kika ก่อนที่จะใช้คุณลักษณะนี้"</string>
     <string name="terms_of_use_lable_gms">, Google Play services</string>
     <string name="terms_of_use_lable_smart_cards">, Smart cards</string>
     <string name="terms_of_use_lable_vsimcore">, MConnService</string>
     <string name="terms_privacy_policy_input_method_facemoji">นโยบายความเป็นส่วนตัว Facemoji</string>
     <string name="terms_privacy_policy_input_method_kika">นโยบายความเป็นส่วนตัว Kika</string>
     <string name="title_fingerprint">ตั้งรหัสผ่าน</string>
     <string name="user_agreement">ข้อตกลงและเงื่อนไขการใช้งาน</string>
     <string name="user_agreement_declare">Before using MIUI, you must read and agree to our User Agreement and Privacy Policy. While your device is being activated, Mi SIM Activation Service, Home screen, Frequent phrases, Translation Service, MIUI Daemon, and Updater will connect to the network. MSA will connect to the network and access your location.</string>
     <string name="voice_assist_advice">Mi AI อณุญาตให้คุณใช้การควบคุมด้วยเสียง แต่จะใช้พลังงานมากกว่าเดิม (+1% ทุกชั่วโมง)</string>
     <string name="voice_assist_condition">"คุณจะสามารถใช้งาน Mi AI ได้ในกรณี:
1. เมื่อหน้าจอเปิดอยู่
2. เมื่อคุณกำลังฟังเพลงในขณะปิดหน้าจอ"</string>
     <string name="voice_assist_desp">พูด \"Mi AI\" ลงในโทรศัพท์ของคุณ Mi AI จะจดจำเสียงของคุณและจะสามารถควบคุมอุปกรณ์ของคุณได้</string>
     <string name="voice_assist_title">ปลุกด้วยเสียง</string>
     <string name="welcome">ยินดีต้อนรับ</string>
     <string name="wizard_script_uri">android.resource://com.android.provision/raw/wizard_script</string>
     <string name="zone_picker_title">เลือกเขตเวลา</string>
</resources>